http://www.fullcirclepadding.com/service/privacy/

Skip to main content
file-pdf
Quotes are only good for 30 days
The site navigation utilizes arrow, enter, escape, and space bar key commands. Left and right arrows move across top level links and expand / close menus in sub levels. Up and Down arrows will open main level menus and toggle through sub tier links. Enter and space open menus and escape closes them as well. Tab will move on to the next part of the site rather than go through menu items.
Menu
Pads & Parts By BrandReplacement PartsAnti-Slip Grip TapeBelting for Weight StacksBike Seats and Pedal StrapsCable Supplies and ToolsDumbbell, Weight Stack and Plate StickersFoam RollersFreeweight Parts Weight Stack Parts Caps, Belting, Pop Pins,Screw KnobsGrips, Aluminum Grip Caps and Aluminum Grip CollarsPlastic & Rubber Frame Caps, Tips & StopsPop Pin Assemblies, Knobs & SpringsPulleysSet Screw CollarsStretchMateThreaded & Screw Down KnobsTools and Repair Kits Upholstery, Retaining Rings, NutsertsVinyl by the Linear Yard or RollWeight Stack Parts, Decal Stickers & Add-on WeightsWeight Stack Selector PinsAccessoriesAquatic Fitness ProductsBalls, Ball Racks and Air PumpsCable AttachmentsCleaning and Lubricating ProductsCLEARANCECore, Balance and Stretch TrainingDumbbell, Barbell and Kettlebell RacksDumbbells, Kettlebells, Dumbbell Handles and Dumbbell StickersFitness ChartsGroup & Aerobics ExerciseKettlebellsLat BarsNylon Stirrup Handles & StrapsOlympic Bars, Bar Stands, Collars and Bar PadsOlympic Weight PlatesPersonal TrainingPower LiftingPromotional ProductsRacks and StandsResistance TrainingScales & DiagnosticsStretch MatsSuspension TrainingTreadmill,
Elliptical and Bike MatsTricep AttachmentsWeight BeltsYogaProtective PaddingEZ Flex MatsRubber FlooringWall, Floor and Backboard PaddingCable BuilderVinyl MaterialFull Circle Padding's Stock Vinyl Colors by the YardBoltaFlex Color Guard Vinyl by the YardBoltaFlex Color Guard by the 30 Yard RollNaugahyde Spirit Millennium by the Yard Naugahyde Spirit Millennium by the 30 Yard RollBoltaFlex Grand Sierra by the YardBoltaFlex Grand Sierra by the 30 Yard RollFCP Black Vinyl by the YardFCP Black Vinyl by the RollImpact 16oz Premium Coated VinylVinyl Tex 18oz Vinyl Coated Polyester FabricRubber Sheeting by the Yard or Square FootDIY Tools & SuppliesFoam by the SheetFoam by the Square FootSpray AdhesiveStaple on Covers by the RollTools and Repair KitsHardwareFCP MerchFCP MerchandiseFCP Apparel
(800) 875-7780
Privacy Policy
Protecting your privacy is important to Full Circle Padding. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Full Circle Padding Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. Full Circle Padding will never, under any circumstances, make your personal information available to any third parties. Contact information (including e-mail address) is never sold, nor shared through any operational or billing procedures. In the rare case of a legal investigation, Full Circle Padding will cooperate fully with local, state, and federal law enforcement agencies.
Why We Collect Personal Information...
FullCirclePadding.com may collect and use your personal information to give you superior service, to provide you with convenient access to our services, to contact you with additional questions when signing up for any of our offerings.
How We Collect Personal Information...
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you request information on our site. Or, if you ask to be included in an email mailing list, we collect and store information you provide in a secure database.
How We Protect Your Personal Information...
Full Circle Padding safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, managerial and electronic procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.
Collecting Other Personal Information...
When you browse the FullCirclePadding.com website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address.
Like many websites, the FullCirclePadding.com website uses "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.
Our Company Wide Commitment to Privacy...
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Full Circle Padding employee.
Full Circle Padding does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.
Full Circle Padding contains links to other sites. Full Circle Padding and/or FullCirclePadding.com does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.
If you have not given us your permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.
The Full Circle Padding Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
